你知道大家都讲关于我们的传闻吗
Did you know people tell stories about us?
是啊 看来我们还算是传奇人物
Yeah. Apparently, we're a little bit legendary.
（走过的路）
- 我们开始吧 - 妈妈
- Let's begin. - ‭Mom?
我一直在跟英国记录者合作
I have sort of been working with the British Men of Letters.
我知道你多恨他们
I know how much you hate them.
不 我们恨他们 我们都恨他们
No, we hate them. Us. Together.
路西法回来了
Lucifer is back.
克劳力死了
Crowley's dead,
魔鬼去找他儿子了
and the Devil is out looking for his son.
一个拿非利人要诞生了
A nephilim is come into being.
我能感觉到 我是它的母亲
I can feel it. I'm its mother.
我的宝宝不是邪恶的
My baby's not evil.
他给我看了未来
He showed me the future.
- 怎么… - 我有了信心
- How? - ‭I have faith…
- 别 - 这个孩子
- Don't. - …in this child.
她会开枪的
She will shoot you.
玛丽
Mary.
（如今）
上帝 求你
God, please.
我需要帮助
I need help.
我是在帮你 女士
I'm trying to help you, ma'am.
是吗 斯文
Are you, Sven?
因为如果你再问一次 我是不是有
Because if you ask me if I have the quarter-inch Allen wrench.
四分之一英寸的通用扳手 我就要过去
one … one more time, I am going to come down there.
烧毁你们的垃圾维京商店
and burn your giant Viking junkyard of a store to the ground!
你明白吗
Do you understand?!
你确定它不在盒子里吗
Are you sure it wasn't in the box?
天呐
God!
凯莉
Kelly.
我说过我会组装好的
I told you I'd put this together.
我很擅长遵从指示
I'm very good at following instructions.
- 你需要休息 - 不 我不需要
- And you need to rest. - No, I don't.
- 凯莉 - 不 小卡 我不需要
- Kelly - No, Cass, I don't.
我不能
I can't.
我不知道还要多久就会
I don't know how long until…
我不知道我还剩多久
I don't know how long I have left.
我永远没机会教他骑自行车
And I…I'm never gonna be able to teach him how to ride a bike.
或是看着他结婚
or watch him get married.
甚至是看他的眼睛
or even look him in the eyes.
但我可以给他做个破瑞典摇篮
But I can build him a stupid Swedish crib!
这我可以做到
I can do that.
凯莉 我知道这多难
Kelly, I know how hard this is.
不对
That's a lie.
我无法想象 这对你有多难
I have no idea how hard this is for you.
但我保证
But I promise you…
我会尽全力
I will do everything.
我愿为你儿子献出生命
I will give my life for your son.
我会养大他
And I will raise him.
我会让他成为你能引以为傲的人
And I will make him someone you will be proud of.
我知道
I know.
好了 我理理清楚
Okay, let me just get this straight.
我们打败了英国人
So… we beat the Brits,
我们打败了这帮爱喝茶的疯子
we kicked their psycho, tea-swilling asses,
我们不能打开一瓶香槟 去赌城庆祝
and instead of popping champagne and headin' to Vegas,
- 还要对付路西法 - 你确定是他吗
- we get Lucifer. - And you're sure it's him?
嗯 那是他的旧皮囊
Yeah. That's his old vessel, too.
- 这怎么可能 - 克劳力吧
- How is that possible? - Crowley, I guess.
现在他死了
And now he's dead.
海斯是这么说的
Well, that's what Hess said.
但克劳力是个小强
But Crowley's a freakin' cockroach.
等我见到尸体 把他烧了 才会相信
I'll believe he's gone when I see the body and burn it.
这要疼了
This is gonna hurt.
我们不需要克劳力 我们需要罗威娜
We don't need Crowley. We need Rowena.
是她把路西法关回了笼子
I mean, she's the one who can slam Lucifer back into the Cage.
太好了 她在哪
Great. So where is she?
（萨姆·温彻斯特）
萨姆
Oh, hey, Sammy.
[邪恶力量 第12季第23集]
怎么了
What?
如果你们找罗威娜
Oh, if you're looking for Rowena,
她现在抱恙
she is presently indisposed.
就是委婉地说
Which is a delicate way of saying,
我踩她踩到她大脑爆浆
I stomped on her face till the white meat showed,
然后又把她烧成炭 以防万一
and then set her on fire, just in case.
红发女人啊
Gingers.
场面凌乱
It was messy and…
她还各种叫唤 但没办法 萨姆
screamy, but it had to be done, Sam.
我就要当爹了
I'm about to be a dad.
待在牢笼里要怎么养儿子啊
Can't raise the little nipper from a jail cell now, can I?
说到这个
Speaking of…
你知道你的小伙伴卡西迪奥在哪吗
you know where your little pal Castiel is?
下地狱去吧
Go to hell.
真幽默 我将来会借用的
Good one. Witty. I'll use that in the future.
那好吧
All right, well,
我也想多聊聊 但是
I'd love to chat with ya, but, uh,
何必浪费时间呢
why waste my time, right?
你又不重要
It's not like you matter.
我不需要再披上萨姆的肉身了
I don't need to put on the old Sam suit anymore, do I?
0你如果以为我们会就这么放过你
You know, if you think we're just gonna let you walk …
好啊 迪恩
Oh, hey, Dean!
我知道你们会试着…什么的
I know you fellas are gonna try, you know, whatever.
不管你们打算干什么
Whatever you're gonna try.
但你们杀不了我
But you can't kill me.
你们一直没能杀掉我
You've never been able to kill me.
女巫贱人一死 你们也不能把我关回笼子了
And with, uh, witch bitch gone, you can't put me back in the Cage,
所以就像我说的
so like I said…
你们不重要了
you don't matter.
好吗
Okay?
再见 再见
Buh-bye. Buh-bye.
再见 亲爱的
Bye, dear.
我就是说
I'm just saying,
收银员看我们的样子好像我们很奇怪
the checkout guy looked at us like we were super weird.
你会习惯的
Ah, you'll get used to it.
好吧 但是 小卡 你有点过头了
Okay, but…Cass, I mean, you went a little overboard.
我不同意
I disagree.
我读了74本关于育儿的书
I have read 74 books on child rearing,
有一件事是他们都达成一致的
and there is one thing that they all agree on …
所有人都拉屎
everybody poops.
你没说错
Well, you're not wrong.
我没事 我…
I'm fine. I'm…
我没事
I'm fine.
路西法是对的
You know, Lucifer's right.
我们杀不了他 也不能把他关回笼子
We can't kill him and we can't slam his ass back in the Cage.
嗯 好 那我们争取时间
Yeah. Okay. So maybe we play for time.
找到小卡和凯莉 让他们不停转移
Find Cass and Kelly, keep 'em moving.
如果路西法找不到他们 就伤害不了他们
If Lucifer can't find them, he can't hurt them.
你觉得卡西迪奥会配合吗
You think Castiel is gonna go along with that?
你觉得我们会让他有的选吗
You think we'll give him a choice?
孩子呢
And the baby?
希望我们还能吸走它的能量
Hopefully, we can still siphon off its grace.
如果不行 我们就再想办法
If not, uh… we'll figure something else out.
最好是
Yeah, we better.
那好
All right, then.
我一直想揍魔鬼来着
Kind of always wanted to punch the Devil in the face.
我们怎么找到他们
So how do we find them?
好吧 我们知道凯莉很快就要生了
All right, look, we know Kelly's gonna have that kid soon.
很快了 根据传说
Like, really soon. And according to the lore,
拿非利人出生时 会有迹象
whenever a nephilim is born, there are signs.
暴风雨 疾病爆发
Uh, storms, outbreaks of disease,
- 蝗灾 - 《圣经》里那样
- uh, plague of locusts. - Things get Biblical.
没错 这么多能量进入世界
Exactly. That much power into the world,
不管在哪 不管何时发生
whenever and wherever it happens,
肯定会出现诡异现象
things get weird.
那么我们要找奇怪的现象
So we're looking for something…weird.
是啊 这辈子不都如此
Yeah. Story of our lives.
这是哪
Where…
怎么会
How…
你
You?
杰克 是…
Hi, Jack. It's, uh…
是你妈妈
I'm your mom.
我知道你不会有事的
I know you're gonna be okay.
你会
You are gonna be…
很棒的
amazing.
有个天使会守护你呢
You have an angel watching over you.
天呐 我爱你 杰克
God, I love you, Jack.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
对不起
Sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
听听
Hey, listen to this …
爱达荷州熔岩温泉村有双头小牛诞生
two-headed calf was born in Lava Hot Springs, Idaho.
挺奇怪吧
That's weird.
是挺奇怪
That is weird.
是啊 但不是我们要的那种
Yeah, but not our kind of weird.
听着 不管这玩意会是什么样
Look, whatever this thing is gonna be,
都会很厉害 很坏
it … it's gonna be big and bad …
你们找我
You rang?
你们好啊
Hello, boys.
是你干的吗
Did you do it?
是你放路西法出来的吗
Did you let Lucifer out?!
- 我没「放」他 - 别
- I didn't "let" - ‭Don't!
小鹿 帮帮忙
Moose, a little help here!
迪恩 等等
Dean, wait.
- 不是吧 - 不是吧
- Seriously? - ‭Seriously?
别杀他
Look, just don't kill him.
他跟罗威娜一起研究过笼子咒语 或许能帮忙
He worked the Cage spell with Rowena. Maybe he can help us.
- 如果他不能呢 - 那时我们再杀他
- And what if he can't? - Well, then we kill him.
笼子咒语
Cage spell?
那不是妈妈的工作吗
Thought you had mother for that.
罗威娜死了
Rowena's dead.
真的
Really?
是啊 真的
Yeah, really.
是路西法
Lucifer.
有意思
Funny.
我一直以为杀她的会是我
I always thought I'd be the one to kill her.
克劳力 你为什么那么做
Crowley…why did you do it?
救路西法 你想干什么
Save Lucifer … What did you want?
我想赢
I wanted to win.
我修改了母亲的咒语
I perverted mother's spell,
把路西法放入了我自己做的皮囊里
put Lucifer in a vessel of my own making.
因为我想赢
because I wanted to win.
你知道有多少人
You have any idea how many people.
这些年来曾企图篡夺我的王位吗
have made a play for my throne over the years?
路西法 阿比顿
Lucifer, Abaddon,
等等等等
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
太多了
Too damn many.
我想 如果我能控制住魔鬼
I thought if I could put the Devil on a leash…
做我的私人核武器
my own personal nuke,
就再不会有人来挑衅我了
no one would ever dare challenge me again.
是啊 看结果多好
Yeah. That worked out great.
结果我躲在老鼠里才勉强逃过一劫
All ended with me narrowly escaping death by hiding in a rat.
等等
Wait.
真老鼠吗
In an…actual rat?
其实也没那么糟
Wasn't too bad, really.
给了我时间思考
Gave me time to think.
长久以来 我都致力于保住我的工作
You know, I've been focused for so long on keeping my job.
从未意识到 我讨厌它
Never realized I hate it.
那些叽叽歪歪的恶魔
All those whining demons,
诅咒灵魂无穷无尽的哀嚎
the endless moan of damned souls,
还有文书工作
the paperwork!
谁想要那个啊
I mean, who wants that?
你
You.
或许曾经吧
Once, maybe.
那你来做什么
So why are you here?
每当出现世界终结的危机
Well, whenever there's a world-ending crisis at hand,
我知道该押注在谁身上
I know where to place my bets.
你们
It's on you,
你们这群美丽
you big, beautiful,
迟钝的法兰绒糙汉
lumbering piles of flannel.
如果你们能原谅我的过失
So if you'll forgive my transgression,
我不会亏了你们的
I'll make it worth your while.
什么意思
Which means?
等我们把路西法关回笼子
After we put Lucifer back in his cage …
当然是通力合作
together …
我会关闭地狱大门
I'll seal the gates of Hell.
你们再不会见到一个恶魔了
You'll never see another demon again,
当然 除了我
apart from, of course, yours truly.
你愿那么做
You would do that?
何不呢 他们背后捅我刀
Why not? They stab me in the back,
我很乐意正面 侧面
I'll happily stab them in the front, the sides,
下面回敬他们
and right up their little black-eyed asses.
那么
So…
成交吗
we have a deal?
小卡
Cass?
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
凯莉
Kelly.
你去哪了
Where were you?
我…
I, um…
没去哪
uh, nowhere.
一切都好吗
Um, is everything okay?
不好
No.
宝宝
The baby, it's…
好像要生了
I think it's time.
天呐
Oh, my God.
- 看着我 - 天呐
- Look at me. - ‭Oh, God.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
我不在的时候你们就做这个吗
This is what you do when I'm not here?
打字
Type?
对
Yep.
等等 有发现
Wait a second. I got something.
两小时前 太平洋西北部地区
Okay, two hours ago, there was a massive power outage.
发生大面积停电
in the Pacific Northwest.
听上去正是我们要的怪异
Sounds like the right kind of weird.
是啊 等等
Oh, yeah. Wait.
经追踪 断电起源点在
They tracked the outage to an address.
华盛顿州北湾
in North Cove, Washington,
一栋目前由詹姆斯·诺瓦克
to a house currently being rented.
租的房屋
by one James Novak.
那是小卡 走吧
That's Cass. Let's roll.
可是时候了
It's about time.
你做了那样的事 还指望我们信任你吗
Think we're gonna trust you out there after what you pulled?
不 你留下 坐那儿 闭嘴
No. You stay here, you sit down, and you shut up.
你没事的
You're all right.
阵压频率还远远不够高
The pressure waves are still very far apart.
「阵压」
"Pressure waves"?
这是
It's what they …
我导乐分娩课上对「宫缩」的叫法
it's what they called contractions in my doula class.
我在网上学的
I-I took it online.
初次妈妈 生产可能要12到18小时
First-time mothers, labor can be 12 to 18 hours,
有时要更久
sometimes longer.
不过 鉴于这是路西法的儿子
Although, given this is the child of Lucifer.
还是类神生物
and a quasi-celestial being…
网上没有相关教程吗
They didn't cover that online?
没有
They did not.
小卡
Cass?
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你做的一切
For everything.
不客气
Of course.
凯莉
Kelly.
再跟我说说
Tell me again.
再跟我说说你看到的
Tell me again what you saw.
好 我看到
Right, I saw … I saw…
我看到了未来
I saw the future.
一个没有痛苦的世界
I saw a world without pain.
没有饥饿和贫困
or hunger or want.
我看到这孩子
I saw the world that this child…
你的孩子
that your child… ‭
将创造的世界
will create.
这个世界
And it is a world.
没有恐惧 没有痛苦
without fear and without suffering.
没有仇恨
and without hate.
我看到了天堂
I saw paradise.
迪恩
Dean?
小卡 这地方有符文吗
Cass, is this place warded?
- 有 很多 - 足以抵挡路西法吗
- Yes, heavily. - Heavy enough to stop Lucifer?
路西法
Lucifer?
他可能后脚就到
He could be right behind us.
我不…
I don't…
- 你们来干什么 - 救你
- What are you doing here? - Saving your ass.
你和凯莉这么跑掉很愚蠢
Look, you and Kelly just taking off was a stupid move.
但我们绝不能让路西法
But there's no way we're letting Lucifer.
得到那个孩子
get his hands on that kid.
绝对不能
It ain't happening.
萨姆是对的
Look, Sam's right, okay?
我们一向能理清我们的破事
We'll work through our crap. We always do.
但现在 我们要来带你
But right now, we are here to get you,
带上凯莉 然后离开
get Kelly, and get gone.
她不能走动了 她要…
She can't be moved. She's having a …
我去看她
I'll check on her.
我们还有多少时间
How much time do we have?
我们不知道
We don't know.
如果他来了
Hey, if he shows,
你能不能再冒一次火
can you flame on again?
你能不能像对付大衮那样烧了路西法
Can you torch Lucifer like you did Dagon?
我不知道
I don't know. No,
不 那不是我 是那孩子
that wasn't me. That was the child.
如果你还没发现
And in case you haven't noticed,
他挺忙的
he's a little busy.
该死
Son of a bitch.
来 迪恩
Here, Dean.
我来吧
Let me.
谢了
Thanks.
好吧 我们该复查一下符文
All right, we should double-check the warding.
等等
Wait.
好吧 那个 如果我们…
Right. So listen, if we, uh…
小卡 那是什么
Cass? What is that?
是时间空间的裂口
It's a tear in space and time.
什么意思
Uh, and that means?
是通往另一个世界的门
It's a doorway to another world.
什么 纳尼亚吗
Anoth… What, like Narnia?
不是 那一边也是地球
No. No, through there it's Earth,
但不一样
but…but different.
是平行世界
It's a … it's an alternate reality.
是疯狂世界喽
So it's a Bizarro world?
或是 之前我们被传送去的那个世界
Or … or like the place we got zapped to where we were, uh,
- 我们是电视剧里的演员 - 是啊
- uh, actors on a TV show. - Oh, yeah.
- 那个没有凶鬼恶灵的地方 - 是啊
- The supernatural wasn't real. - Yeah.
- 你还是波兰裔 - 对
- And you were Polish. - R-right.
等等 小卡
Wait, Cass,
这玩意怎么来的
how did this get here?
这孩子的降生
Well, the child being born,
他的能量 似乎
his power, it seems to be.
撕裂了我们世界的结构
puncturing the fabric of our universe.
太好了
Awesome.
是啊
Yeah.
那么另一边里有什么
And what exactly is on the other side?
你不想知道的
You don't wanna know.
或许吧
Probably.
但我们必须知道
But we need to.
小卡 这怎么回事
Cass, what is this?
我说了 这里是地球
As I said, it's … it's Earth.
但这个地球陷入了
But this Earth is locked in eternal war.
天堂和地狱的永恒战争之中
between Heaven and Hell. There are.
天使大军跟成群恶魔大战
armies of angels fighting hoards of demons, and.
仅剩的一些人类被夹在了中间
the few humans that remain are caught in between.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
一个朋友告诉我的
A friend told me.
很好 你还交朋友了 真是…
Oh, good. Now you're makin' friends? That's…
好吧 从1到10打分 情况有多糟
All right, on a scale of 1 to 10, how bad is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
我得说
I gotta say, a, uh,
现实裂开一道缝通往一个被天启毁灭的世界
hole in reality to a bombed out Apocalypse world?
我要打11分
I'm gonna go with 11.
差不多
Sounds right.
不用担心
You don't have to worry.
是那孩子打开了大门
The child, he opened this door.
他也能关上
He'll close it.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我有信心
I have faith.
是吗 信仰你那个未出生的婴儿上帝
Really? In your unborn baby-God?
是的
Yes.
那你是个蠢蛋
Well, then, you're a dumbass.
伙计们
Guys. Guys!
- 手举起来 - 别
- Hands in the air! - No. Don't.
鲍比
Bobby?
我认识你吗
Do I know nou?
鲍比
Bobby…
我是萨姆
Sam.
这是迪恩和小卡
Dean. Cass.
听你的口气
You say that like.
好像我该知道 但…
it's supposed to mean something to me, but…naw.
萨姆 这是鲍比
Sam, this is Bobby,
但不是你那个鲍比
but it's your B…
鲍比 是我们
Bobby, it's us.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester.
我只听说过约翰·温彻斯特
The only Winchester I ever heard of was John.
是啊 约翰·温彻斯特 我们的父亲
Yeah. John Winchester, our father.
我深表怀疑 他都死了
Doubt it. He's dead.
死了40多年了
Been dead over 40 years now.
我会知道他是因为我一个猎人朋友
Only reason I know about him is this Hunter I ran with,
玛丽·坎贝尔
Mary Campbell.
你请她喝几杯
You get a few pints of shine into her,
她总会讲同一个故事
and she always told the same story about the.
她的挚爱 约翰·温彻斯特
man she loved … John Winchester.
大概十年前 她被亚撒色杀了
Azazel killed her about 10 years ago.
小卡 这什么情况
Cass, what the hell is this?
这是你们没出生的世界
This is a world where you were never born.
是你们没拯救的世界
It's a world you never saved.
好吧
Okay.
现在间隔不到五分钟了
I think they're less than five minutes apart now.
时候就要到了
It's almost time.
你怎么样了
How you doin'?
我要死了
I'm dying.
我知道
I know.
但没关系
But that's okay.
换了你不会为儿子牺牲吗
'Cause wouldn't you die for your sons?
是啊
Yeah.
这个
When this…
不知是什么裂开后
whatever opened up,
我那里各种警铃大作
all sorts'a alarms went off back at my place.
我赶到时
I got here just in time.
正好看到你们的朋友被一个诱惑恶魔袭击
to see your boy get ambushed by a tempter demon.
什么
A what?
是
It's, um…
黑眼 尖牙
black eyes, pointed teeth,
牛角
horns.
等等 恶魔还长角了
Wait a second. Demons have horns now?
新世界 萨姆
Whole new world, Sam.
我一般看到天使就击毙
Usually I gun down flyboys on sight.
但是
But, uh,
他看上去
he looked…
不一样
different.
至少没戴婴儿耳朵做的项链
Wasn't wearing a necklace made out of baby ears, for one thing.
我们谈了起来 我讲了我来自哪里
We got to talking about where I came from and our.
还有我们的两个世界
two worlds.
就他的话
From what he says,
你们那边可美好得很
pretty much peaches and cream on your side.
倒也未必
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
但总比这里强
It's better than this.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
这里也不赖 如果你喜欢杀天使
Ain't so bad here, if you like killing angels.
你喜欢吗
And you do?
是我的爱好
It's my hobby.
和热爱
and my passion.
所以
So…
我觉得 楼上的混蛋
I figured, it's only a matter of time.
迟早会得知这事
before the dicks upstairs get wind'a this.
等他们来了
And when they show…
我和鲁弗斯就开工
me and Rufus go to work.
这里有百发子弹
He's loaded with a hundred rounds,
是旧天使之刃锻造的
cast from old angel blades.
等等 杀天使的子弹
Wait, angel-killing bullets?
太赞了
Awesome.
好了
Okay.
没事
你没事的
‭You're okay.
你们没事吧
Are you all right?
有事 小卡
No, Cass.
我完全不是没事
Pretty far from all right.
这边有路西法
I mean, we've got Lucifer on this side,
那边是疯狂麦克斯的世界
we've got Mad Max World on that side.
我们以前也落魄过 但这个
I mean, yeah, we've been down before, but this?
我都不知道该从哪开始吐槽
I-I mean, I don't even know where to start.
拜托
Oh, come on!
你们好 又见面了
Hello, boys. Again.
等等 你怎么
Wait a second, how the hell did you …
即兴发挥
I improvised.
幸亏了
Lucky I did.
看来我能解决你们的一切问题
Turns out I'm the answer to all your problems.
我可以跟她说话吗
May I speak with her?
当然
Sure.
玛丽
Mary.
我就回来
I'll be back.
好
Okay.
小卡
Cass…
怎么了
what's wrong?
你准备好了吗
You ready?
没有
Nope.
那什么时候让我们迟疑了
When has that ever stopped us?
是啊
Yeah.
小卡对那孩子有信心
You know, Cass has faith in this kid.
希望他是对的
I hope he's right. ‭
但我呢
But me?
我相信我们
I have faith in us.
你 我 妈妈 小卡
You, me, Mom, Cass.
还有克劳力 有时候吧
And Crowley. Sometimes.
这会成功的
This is gonna work.
必须成功
It has to.
别担心
Don't worry.
不会有事的
It will be fine.
记住
Remember.
天堂
paradise.
哎呀
Well…
真是意外之喜
this is a fun surprise.
我得承认
I gotta hand it to you guys.
你们真是从不放弃
You never give up,
哪怕你们该放弃
even when you should.
哪怕不放弃是非常愚蠢的
Even when it would be so stupid not to.
听着 不管你打算做什么
Look, whatever you're planning on doing,
恰克
Chuck…
上帝会阻止你的
God will stop you,
就像上次那样
just like he did last time.
你是对的
You're right.
我该怎么办啊
What should I do?
上帝 别劈死我啊
Oh, God! Don't strike me dead!
得了 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
你就像耶稣营里的处子
You sound like a virgin in Jesus camp.
「不行 上帝看着呢」
"We can't. God is watching."
不
No.
恰克「走了」 他不在了
Chuck "walked." He's gone.
那你就要砸坏他的玩具吗
So you're just gonna smash his toys?
没错
Exactly.
因为每次我看着这可悲的破烂世界
'Cause every time I look at this sad trash fire of a world,
知道我怎么想的吗
you know what I keep thinking?
我可以做得更好
I could do so much better.
那么天启2.0 这就是你的计划
So Apocalypse, take two. That's your plan?
如果有迟疑 总是选经典
When in doubt, go with the classics.
我一向这么说
That's what I always say.
好了 各位
Well, boys,
前戏到此为止吧
enough with the foreplay.
我们开始
Let's do this.
另一边见 各位
See you on the other side, boys.
真厉害
Well, that worked.
成熟
Mature.
好成熟啊
Real mature!
各位
You guys?
我真的想好好打一顿的
I really want to enjoy this.
我真的很想好好撕碎你们
Really wanna savor just ripping you apart,
弄得满手血污
gettin' all up in there, and gettin' all gooey.
但是
But, you know,
那小家伙就要出生了
little slugger's almost here and, uh…
我时间紧迫
Well, I'm on the clock.
有意思
Interesting.
不错啊
Nice.
你想要天启
You wanted the Apocalypse?
这里就是
You got it.
萨姆
Sammy.
你哥哥呢
Where's your big bro?
这里
Right here.
好玩具
Sweet toy.
是啊 从一个老
Yeah, I got it off an old …
新朋友手里要来的
new pal of mine.
瞧 我们打了个赌
See, we have this bet,
看这玩意对付大天使好不好使
see if it works against an archangel.
那么
So…
跟我的小伙伴们打招呼吧
say hello to my little friend.
可算来了
Took you long enough.
别闹 克劳力 快点
Not now, Crowley. Come on.
好样的
‭Yeah, baby!
来吧
Come on!
我们举行仪式 封闭裂缝
We do this ritual, we seal that rift,
然后把魔鬼关在这个鬼地方
and we lock the Devil in this godforsaken place.
计划是这样的 记得吗
That's the plan, remember?
一咒语二鸟
Two birds, one spell.
是啊 快点
Right, right. Just hurry.
你输了
‭You lose.
死海盐
Dead Sea brine,
水银 羔羊血 圣油
mercury, lambs blood, holy oil.
好了
Here we go.
就这些了 都齐了
That's the last of it. That's everything.
- 还没有 - 什么
- No, it's not. - ‭What?
想封闭裂缝
If we wanna seal that rip,
我们还需要一样小原料
we need one more minor ingredient.
- 什么 - 一条生命
- What? - ‭A life.
我可以玩一整天呢
Ah, I could do this all day.
你的叫声好搞笑
You make such funny noises.
惊喜
Surprise.
克劳力
Crowley!
你个狡猾的小…
You sneaky little…
看来我可以杀你两次了 克劳力
So I guess I get to kill you twice, huh, Crowley?
我深表怀疑
I doubt it.
不不 你有机会的
Oh, no, no. You had your chance.
你本可以把我关回笼子 但是
You could've put me back in the Cage, but…
你非得跟我斗气 是吧
you had to make it personal, didn't you?
没错
You're right.
就是要争口气
It is personal.
你侮辱了我
You humiliated me.
我…
I…
我非常恨你
I hate you. Deeply.
真心恨你
Truly.
我会很享受让你那
I'm gonna enjoy wiping that.
自鸣得意的笑容消失
smug, self-satisfied look off your face.
我会亲自做到
Personally.
你是说
You mean…
这个吗
this one?
得了 克劳力 你知道你不管做什么
Come on, Crowley. You know whatever you try,
都会输的
you're gonna lose.
没错
You're right.
再见了 小伙子们
Bye, boys.
小卡
Cass?
- 不不 快走 - 小卡
- No, come on. Come on! - Cass!
- 小卡 不不不
- Cass! Cass! ‭- No, no, no, no, no, no!
我们得走了
We gotta go! We gotta go!
我爱你
I love you.
小卡
Cass.
不
No!
真好玩
That was fun.
真的 努力可嘉
Seriously, guys, points for trying.
我非常钦佩 但是
Super impressed, but, uh…
游戏时间结束了
playtime's over.
离他们远点
Get away from them.
玛丽 是吧
Mary, right?
嗯 我听说过你
Yeah, I've heard about you.
你
You, uh,
真是名不虚传
are certainly living up to the hype.
真的 我想感谢你
Look, seriously, I just wanted to say thank you.
做的一切
for everything.
我欠你的 丫头
I owe ya, kid.
妈妈
Mom, Mom, Mom.
我爱你们
I love you.
真可爱
Cute.
就这点本事吗 妈妈
Is that all you got, mama?
妈妈
‭Mom!
- 妈妈 不 - 不不
- Mom, Mom! No! - No! No!
不不
No, no! No!
不
No!
No.
不不
No, no, no, no, no.
（杰克）